This video is sponsored by Tero Hutton
who makes the invisible investable CEO
barbecue origenic gold exploration in
northwestern Ontario as well as a bunch
of other stuff together with Harfang
Exploration. But if you're short on
time, subscribe to our free newsletter
and once a week we'll send you a 5-minut
summary of all interviews we put out
resources.com
for a free weekly newsletter. Now,
although this company has not paid us
for the production of this video, you
should still understand that we are not
financial adviserss and this is not
intended as financial advice. It is a
broad, general, and impersonal piece of
information intended only for those who
know and understand the risks of junior
mining, of which there are many. Before
moving on, read the company's official
filings on sitterplus.ca and do your own
due diligence. Pause the screen and read
all the disclaimers I've shown you
because your capital is at risk. If this
isn't clear, go to the last section of
this video for a longer explanation of
the risks and biases. And do not consume
this content if you don't agree with
everything said therein. Moving on, our
fang's flagship is the Sky Lake project.
It's an well, at least I I should
actually preface this by saying I think
it might be the the the flagship, but I
haven't spoken to them about it yet.
Maybe it's not. Um, Sky Lake though is
an origenic gold system sitting about 35
km southwest of the town of Pickle Lake
again in northwestern Ontario where
historic operators outlined a small so
it's it's it's historic. It's
non-compliant but they outlined a small
pod uh decades ago and and then they
largely walked away which of course is
something that I I intend on asking
about later on. There were some
confirmation holes drilled last year in
2025 that showed continuity in one of
the high-grade shoots there. But the
entire program is now on hold while
they're working on a traditional
knowledge and land use study required by
one of the first nations in the region.
So we'll definitely talk about that like
how's that going? When can they go back
to drilling are of course questions that
I'll be asking later on today. Again,
there are other projects in this
vehicle, plenty of other projects
actually, the Serpent, there's Maneric,
there's Blake Lock and Egan, but they're
either under option to partners like
Squam Fanamp or there's a non-binding um
Aramat LOI or they're limited to lowc
cost like geohysics and target
generation stuff. So, we'll definitely
talk about all the projects and
hopefully I get to figure out what the
flagship is, if there really even is a
flagship. Now for some of the numbers
and a bit of the details here, Harfang
is listed as HAR. So that's H A on the
TSXV in Canada where the average daily
volume over the last 3 months has been
about 80,000 units. The 52- week high is
12 cents and a 52- week low is 4 cents.
With a little under 115.5 million shares
outstanding and a $5.2 2 million market
cap today. This is a 4.5 cent stock with
a 50 and a 200 day moving average at 5
and 6 cents respectively. So the stock
is now trading below those two. There
are 2.1 million options and 6 million
warrants outstanding which combined
represent about 6.5% of the 123 million
shares on a fully diluted basis. The
last time Harfang and I I should
probably actually stop saying this as a
North American uh but it's actually
pronounced a it means I think it means
snow owl but we we'll talk about that.
They raised the last time they raised
money uh was very recently. It was in in
late July when they closed on a $750,000
financing at 5 cents with a half a
warrant at 10 for 2 years. What's that
money being spent on? How much of it
will go toward GNA versus exploration?
And when's the next time they might need
to raise more capital? Those are all
questions that I'll be asking later on
in the conversation as well. But for
this to actually become a conversation
though, I will already have to shut up
and uh Rick, I'll give you the word. But
first of all, thank you so much for
sitting down with me today.
>> Yeah, thanks for having me. This is uh
this is great. I'm excited to to share
uh everything about about and as you
said, it is it is it does mean snowy
owl. Um, but colloquially in the rest of
in most of the world it's we we call it
Harfang.
>> Well, I don't have that Montreal accent
to say it with. Uh, so I did butcher it
a little bit, but the pleasure is mine.
I'm looking forward to uh hearing the
Harfang story and it's a it really its
current iteration, if you will. May that
might actually make sense to talk about
what it is. What do you guys want to be?
Because you have multiple projects. Some
of them are optioned out. Skylake is
yours, but you're dealing with the First
Nations, as I mentioned before. Do you
see yourself as a prospect generator or
or a pure play explorer code? Yeah. What
do you want to be?
>> Yeah, great question. It's it's funny. I
I'll back up for one second actually.
The two questions that I get asked uh
probably most commonly at the start of
any presentation is uh what's with the
name and what are you guys? So, we've
covered what's with the name. Um and uh
you know and true true to uh true to the
company, the second question is uh what
are you guys what are you guys doing?
And so we are an exploration company. I
can confirm the goal and the business
strategy is an exploration company. Um I
do recognize that we have a lot of uh we
have a lot of assets and you know it
it's easy to label us as a prospect
generator but uh you know at our core we
are a gold exploration company.
>> Right. Okay. Well, then then we should
talk about um all the different projects
and everything as we go. And uh is it
fair to say the Skylake is your
flagship? Do you see it the same?
>> Yeah. Yes. I would say I would say a a
slightly hesitant yes. Um it's really
Skylake or Blake lock. Um the only
reason that I'm hesitant is because we
haven't necessarily drill tested Blake
lock. And you know, this is probably
something that we'll get into later on
in the conversation, but um a at at the
current
at this current day, I would say Skylake
is our flagship with the caveat that
Blake Lock could have the potential to
either become a flagship as well. I'm
not sure if that's kind of kosher in the
mining world to have two flagships, but
uh it could it could either join Skylake
in in in flagship status or it could uh
take over Skylake depending on how the
results go. You know, one thing that's
uh worth pointing out is that a lot of
these both of these are kind of
relatively pre-discovery, very
pre-resource. Um, and so there's still a
lot of room for uh for movement in terms
of which one is the actual flagship.
>> I guess it depends on on how many flag
officers you're going to have and how
big the fleet is. Um, but I think you
can technically have more flagships if
you look at naval history. Um, which
weirdly um, I should probably not care
as much about as I do. But we're going
to talk about all these things um, Rick
that you mentioned here or at least most
of them. But we're going to have to do
the smell test first since this is a
barbecue. And since it is a barbecue,
I'm going to open it up with arguably
the most important question of them all
today. How do you like your steak?
>> I like my steak medium rare.
>> Simple. I like it. Um
>> risky enough to keep the taste, not
risky enough to to to hurt yourself. Um
which is probably a good approach for
exploration as well. Where are you um
where are you from originally? I mean
>> Fair enough. Um the uh the way you said
snowy owl um tells me you might be from
Montreal, but yeah, talk to me about
your background, where you're from
originally. How'd you find your way to
the mining industry?
>> Correct. From Montreal, born and raised.
Um yeah, I lived in Montreal until my
mid20s, traveled the world a little bit,
landed in Toronto. Uh, and then in terms
of how I found myself in the mining
industry, um, I was a young I mean I was
I was when I was a student, I was
actually originally slated to go into
kinesiology. My father's my father's a
physician. Um, I've always been very
active and so, you know, kinesiology
seemed like something that I might be
interested in when I was 17 or 18. You
know, keep in mind in Montreal we have
seep, which is kind of a pre-un
university. And so it's uh it gets you
out of high school a little bit earlier,
a little bit of a different structure
than the rest of Canada. Um so I was
going to go to kinesiology. Uh the the
short story is that I didn't get a place
in residence. Uh I was looking to go to
Calgary. I didn't get a place in
residence. That made me nervous at the
time. And so I pivoted. I stayed in
Montreal. Uh and I went into physical
geography. Uh and that quickly
transitioned into geology. And uh the
reason that I I I ended up there kind of
as my second choice was in CEUP. I took
a geology course that I thought was
incredibly fascinating. I loved it. I
did a little bit more digging. I
realized geology is a mix of the
outdoors and science. And you know, I've
I grew up canoe tripping in Canada. It's
very it's a very popular kind of pastime
here. I love the outdoors and I love
science. And so geology felt like a a
natural fit for someone who uh who's
passionate about the two.
>> I do want to know more about that. But
people listening should also want to
know more about Terra Hutton, who
doesn't only make the invisible
investable, but they've made this video
free of YouTube ads by sponsoring it.
Terra Hutton is built for the people who
are tired of going through boring
PowerPoint decks and geological jargon
when they're analyzing mining companies.
It's a digital platform where the data,
the story, and the context sit together
so mining investors can use visuals to
understand the why without needing a
geology degree or a week off work. And
if you're on the company side, it's a
great way to present your project like a
serious operator with everything
investors keep asking for in one place.
Contact them at terrauden.io.
What about your professional career
since then? Is this um is this the first
time you're the CEO of a public company?
>> This is the first time I'm a CEO. Yeah.
I started my career as a real
exploration geologist, boots on the
ground, uh working in the Arctic looking
for Canadian diamonds uh back in would
have been early 2000s when the diamond
rush was on, you know, deers versus BHP.
It was it was a race. Everyone was
flying around in helicopters. Uh so I
started there and then I I worked a
little bit in the Yukon. I was in
Australia for a bit doing iron ore
exploration. Um, landed up in Toronto,
got into consulting,
focusing really on resource estimation.
I worked with a gentleman here who's I
mean I consider him probably one of the
best, a guy named Mohan Servasta. He's
literally written the book on resource
estimation. There actually is a book
that he wrote. Uh, worked with him for a
little bit and then uh got interested in
finance. You know, I had worked on all
these projects as a exploration
geologist and I, you know, I didn't
really have a a a deep view into the
budget, but I knew that, you know, some
of these projects were hundreds of
thousands to millions of dollars and I I
didn't really understand where this
money was coming from. So, I got
interested in where, you know, h how
does this how does this all work? Whose
money is this? And so I got into
finance, worked in equity research for
uh for a little bit, got an got an MBA
somewhere in there, back to equity
research and following that I put
everything together and I did corporate
development for uh probably about six,
seven years with uh core mining, the
US-based silver producer, and then most
recently I bold and uh yeah, and this is
my first time being the CEO of a uh of a
publicly traded company. you started
working in the industry and your first
thought was who's crazy enough to give
these people any money? I like that. I
like that connection which is also
actually going to be kind of the
thematic of this of this interview as
well. Uh do you do anything else right
now? Is this your your only full-time
position? Do you have any other board
seeds, Seuite, anything like that?
>> Uh I'm a technical adviser to Summit
Royalties, which is uh is a relatively
new vehicle. Um also traded on the TSXV
run by a guy named Drew Clark. uh you
know Drew and I met a long time ago
actually when I was at Core Mining. We
did a deal with with Metallo where he
was previously and so we've kept in
touch and we have a good relationship
and I serve as uh the technical adviser
for him. Uh I'm also the QP for uh for
Summit.
>> Great. I did talk to Drew a while back a
couple of months ago right after they
listed. Did a deep dive with him as well
and I'm uh hopefully we're going to do
some more in the future. Uh how much of
your time goes toward Drew? Um, I know
he can be demanding. So, yeah. How much
of your how much of your time goes
toward Harfang? How much of your time
goes toward Drew?
>> I would say 90 to 95% is Harfang and
about 5% is Drew.
>> Okay.
>> Um, I mean, you know, it it's it's very
dealised
my work with Drew. So, it it varies, but
I'd say 5 to 10% goes to goes to uh to
Summit.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Fair. Um, so this is your
main focus. It sounds like it. What
about skin in the game? How many shares
of Harfang do you own? How did you get
those shares? What's the average cost?
>> I have just over 2 million shares. Um I
picked them up in our most recent
financing at 5 cents with the as you
mentioned with the uh the half warrant.
Um prior to that, I bought a little bit
in the open market. Um but uh I wasn't I
previously wasn't in a financial
position to to take a large chunk right
when I started. So uh h h h h h h h h h
h h h h h h h h h h h h h h h h h h h h
h h h h h h h h h h h hince the delay
till uh till you couple weeks ago,
>> right? Okay, that's all. So all the
shares you have are at 5 cents
basically.
>> Uh yeah. Well, 2 million or 5 cents and
then I have uh you know couple
well a couple maybe a 100,000 at seven
or seven and a half cents. Oh,
>> okay. Well, really what I'm looking for
is is cheap paper. Like does anybody out
there own any cheap paper? Um is it
within management and so on and so
forth? Um yeah is there I mean when when
the company got formed initially did
anybody get any free paper?
>> Uh I don't believe no I don't believe
any free paper was given out obviously
there were options um uh but no no free
paper was given out.
>> Okay. What percentage of the companies
now owned by um reporting insiders?
>> Reporting insiders I would say 10%.
>> Right. Okay. Um
>> yeah. What about the um what about the
rest of the paper? Where's the rest of
the stock? Um yeah, who did your
financing before and and so on?
>> Yeah, so the our biggest shareholders
are the Quebec funds. So we have uh
Sydex, uh we have NQ, uh CDPQ, uh those,
you know, the the the Quebec uh the
Quebec funds, those are by far our
larger shareholders. I mean the the
history of the company is that it was
formed in Quebec uh as a Quebec
exploration vehicle and so uh naturally
the the largest supporters were these
these Quebec funds and they've continued
to support the company.
>> Mhm. What percentage would you guess is
in in kind of non nonfund
hands non insight? So retail essentially
>> retail I'd say about half the shares.
>> Okay. Okay. Fair enough. Yeah. that that
that that probably explains the volume
as well that I went through and then and
obviously little market cap cheap stock
as well. Um so that explains the volume
as well.
>> Do you I'm just kind of gonna keep the
smell test running so we can go and talk
about the you know meat meat and
potatoes of of this barbecue
essentially. Do you personally or
anybody else within the company
personally own a royalty on on any of
the projects you have?
>> No.
>> Yeah. Quick answer. The right answer
too.
>> Yeah. Uh what is the state of all the
projects you have? You have what do you
have? Four projects total I think. Do
you own all of them outright? Is some of
them um options claims? What does that
look like?
>> No, we actually we own all of them
outright. Uh I mean there is a back and
right on Sky Lake um that dates back to
you know prior to when we we acquired
it. Um it's held by Bareric.
>> That's right. Uh other other than that,
no other than that we own we own all
them. Well, I guess actually Pontax
Pontax is now a JV between Harvey and
Lyft. Um I don't necessarily focus that
much on it in my marketing efforts. Um
it is on the website, but uh I guess
that technically is not uh 100% owned by
Harane anymore, but the rest of them are
100% wholly owned by the company.
>> Great. Okay, good. Um I was going to ask
you about roofers and back in, right? uh
you did explain that. We'll talk about
Beric for sure and what that how that
works. What about change of control
fees? Going back to what you told me
earlier. Um if you guys sell the company
tomorrow, what what happens? What what
does management get? What's the payout?
>> Um off the top of my head,
um
to to be honest, and maybe I'm a little
bit embarrassed to say this, but I don't
I don't remember off the top of my head.
>> I don't think it should be mirrors,
actually. If it if it was a thing that
I'm looking for, you would probably
know. Uh what that means is that I'm
typically looking for, you know, red
flags where you guys get 5 million bucks
if you sell the company for 4 million
bucks tomorrow or something like that.
So that that's that's where that comes
from. Um
>> yeah, I mean it's it's it's I guess it's
not significant enough that I remember
it, which is I I guess a a non- red flag
perhaps.
>> Yeah. Well, that that's pretty much what
I what I'm looking for there. Um it's
typically like 24 months of pay or
something like that. Um what is the um
what's the what are the how much money
do you guys make? What what are the what
what are insiders getting?
>> Insiders are getting So my salary is uh
$200,000 a year um discretionary bonus.
Um and then I mean the others are the
the the
general counsel. I mean, our lawyer and
our CFO are both contract. Um, and so
they they get, you know, they're on an
hourly rate and so they get, you know,
depending on the year, but it's probably
in the $150ish,000
per year.
>> Okay. So, nobody's making a million.
>> Obviously, there's just No, no, no, no,
no, no, no. There's discretionary
bonuses and options and stuff. I mean,
it's all in our in our in our, you know,
all in our disclosures, but no, there's
no no one's Yeah. No, no one's uh
feeding a lavish lifestyle off of
Harang.
>> What are the bonuses and options and
everything? What is that based on? So,
what are the KPIs? What does the board
expect from you?
>> Um, we're actually still working that
out. Historically, that really hasn't
been a focus on the company of the
company. um being a very small company
um the I mean the geos get the geos get
performance bonuses based on discovery
um that type of thing uh but in terms of
the seauite um I think it's more
discretionary in terms of the
compensation committee and it's it's
something that we're we're actively
trying to to to document I guess it
hasn't previously been documented you
know before I started
Okay.
Uh why why was there a management change
here in in 2024? What what prompted
that?
>> Uh the previous CEO Ian Campbell, he was
looking to retire. You know, he had had
a a good career. Um and he was looking
to exit and and relax a little bit and
the timing was was right. uh you know
through through uh the the Toronto
Geology Network or the Toronto Mining
Network. Uh he found me and we got into
discussions and it seemed like a good
fit. But no, he was just just looking to
looking to take on the next stage of his
life.
>> Has there been a roll back since or was
there a roll back with that or um or the
name change or Yeah. What did it all
look like?
There was a roll back uh during the
Lasal merger. So when Lasal and Harfang
merged, which is which is where Ian
Campbell came from, there was a roll
back. Uh since I've started, I have not
done a roll back. I don't plan on doing
a roll back. Um I Yeah, it's just not
part of how I operate.
>> Well, it it probably a roll back might
not not be necessarily needed right now.
How long has this company existed for?
Uh this company has existed since the
mid20s.
So since about 20145.
>> So how come it's still like a you know
$5 million market cap company call it.
Um and your price is where it is right
now. What what went wrong essentially in
that 12-year period?
>> Yeah, good question. Uh I mean I think
part of it part of it is marketing. the
company like before I started the
company as far as I could tell had only
been marketed in Quebec. Uh I mean and I
was I was a perfect example. I I live in
Toronto. I'd worked for a number of
other companies doing corporate
development and I was not that familiar
with with Harfang. You know, I'd heard
the name. I wasn't familiar with the
assets. I didn't know the story, you
know, and my job was to to look at
stories globally um and to to you know,
keep tabs on these types of companies.
And so I discovered, you know, very
quickly after I started or actually but
even before I started when I was doing
my due diligence on this company um as
to become the CEO, you know, I the the
the understand the understanding that I
I got was that this company is not well
known outside of Quebec. Inside of
Quebec, it's very very well known. Uh a
lot of people know it.
It has a you know it has a large
following. Outside of Quebec, not very
well known. So I think that's number
one. Um number two is you know something
that we touched on earlier. Are you a
project generator? Are you an
exploration company? A little bit of an
identity crisis. Uh you know in the I
think it was 2020 2021 type thing. Uh
there was a lithium boom and there was
some lithium discovered on the
properties and so the company pivoted to
become a a bit more of a lithium focused
company to ride the lithium wave. um you
know that wave crashed and I think so
did the company a little bit. Uh and so
there's been there's been a bit of an
identity crisis over the last little
while and so that's really where I saw
the opportunity you know when I started
two years ago is to take this company
bring focus to it uh and create an
identity that and a story that people
will understand and wrap their heads
around.
>> Right. Um, in terms of the performance
Oh, sorry. You were going to say
>> I was not. No, I I was just kind of
confirm. I'm listening. I'm actively
listening. People should know that I'm
still not asleep.
>> No, your your eyes are your eyes are
open.
>> There you go.
>> Impressive if you can sleep with your
eyes open. That skill.
>> Um, but uh yeah, in terms of the
performance, I think part of it is the
identity crisis. I mean, I think also
the First Nations situation since the
Sky Lake results. I think that is, you
know, not to be underestimated in terms
of why the shares have underperformed
over over the last little while. We we
were very excited about the results. Um
they were incredible results and then,
you know, we had to put the we had to
put the project on pause and
shareholders, some shareholders don't
like that, don't have the the the
patience for these types of things,
don't understand it. Um, you know, and
with uh with hundreds to thousands of
other junior exploration companies on
the TSX venture, there's no shortage of
of where to put your money.
>> That's that's a good summary and it's a
lot of details that I that I want to
touch upon there. Definitely marketing
is part of it. Obviously, the First
Nation situation is something that I
want to talk about. Rick, I think I'm
through with the smell test though. um
we can actually talk about the more
interesting stuff here which is the
history of the asset and I want to talk
about Sky Lake specifically. So take me
all the way back. I mean Northwestern
Ontario is is a place where a lot of
people have looked already. So what kind
of work has been done here over when was
mineralization first discovered? What
kind of work has been done since?
>> So uh Sky Lake dates back to the I think
it was first found kind of in the 30s. I
actually have a a history slide that I
might reference not necessarily on the
uh uh 1953 gold was discovered. So I was
a little bit off. Um and then it was
discovered through
Yeah. discovered in in in the early 50s.
Uh it was drilled in the 70s and 80s. Uh
actually it was drilled in the 50s as
well. Um so it was drilled kind of in
the 50s 60s7s and 80s. Um
and uh you know this asset changed hands
a number of times. It was in lack
minerals. Lac Minerals was picked up by
Bareric. Uh this asset was was back
burnered. I mean the reality is is this
is not a tier one barrack asset. And so
I don't blame them for putting this on
their back burner. You know a company
like Bareric when they acquire companies
they acquire a lot of stuff that they
don't necessarily care about. Um and so
this was one of them.
>> Uh the previous VPX of Lack Minerals was
uh Dr. Bob Valiant. He's uh my he's one
of my board members. Uh so he was able
to take this asset out of Bareric uh put
it into one of his vehicles. Uh and uh
unfortunately he was not able to
continue meaningful exploration. He did
a little bit of a little bit of uh a
little bit of exploration. Um but he
wasn't able for various reasons to to to
you know put together a significant
drill program. Um and so in terms of
historical historical results, we have
these these results that date back to
the kind of 50s and 60s. These drill
results um interestingly enough, they
were reported in uh dollars per meter
and this was done at $35 gold. And so
Bob and his team uh back in the day when
they when they were doing their work,
they converted the the uh the dollars
per meter. It may have actually even
been dollars per foot back then
>> because I think the imperial system was
more popular in Canada back then. Um and
so they converted into grams per ton uh
you know into the usual grams per ton
over over x number of meters. Uh and so
we have we have that data. There's about
85 to 90 holes that we have. Um I mean
there's a slide uh there's a slide on on
the website which maybe will get
interlaid into this uh into this uh
post-prouction.
>> Uh yeah so we we have that data um and
it's it it's it got me really really
excited about about this asset.
>> Were there any kind of liabilities from
that work? I mean things happened
differently as you said in uh in in the
' 50s for sure. So yeah, were there any
kind of um any kind of liabilities or
anything else that you were left with?
>> No. No. Um actually on the contrary this
this land package was maintained as
patented claims. uh which for for any
viewer who's not familiar with patented
versus unpatented claims in in Ontario
um patented claims are more like
traditional land ownership similar to
how you one would own their house. Um so
we don't actually need permits to drill
on patented claims. Uh it's it's yeah
which is you know on on on one hand it
makes life and logistics a lot easier.
Um, that being said, you know, and we'll
we'll get into the First Nations part of
this uh eventually, I'm sure, but there
are some First Nations implications that
uh I I I have chosen not to overlook.
>> Maybe fast forward to now as well as as
to, you know, how you got this asset.
There's so many companies on on the
Canadian exchanges and and a lot of
people are are looking at Ontario. How
how why are you the chosen one to get
this asset after all this time and work
on it?
>> Yeah. Well, so Bob Valiant, as I said,
he was the uh the previous VPX of Black
Minerals. Um he pulled it out of
Bareric. He put it into his vehicles. Um
and then Harfang
Harfang bought one of his vehicles that
was uh that was they were looking to to
merge or to sell. And so we picked up
his vehicle which had uh the eastern
half of Blake Lock as well as uh
Skylake. And actually the the sto the
the story there if I can d if I digress
a little bit um uh the story where there
was that originally what attracted me to
to new origin uh was consolidating Blake
lock which you know we we'll get into
later but it's 25 kilometer strike
length uh along the Casabardi trend you
know just west of the Casabardi mine
sandwiched between Agniko Eagle uh it
that that was really attractive I that
got me really excited putting together
this these two land packages. You know,
I don't think there's another junior
explorer along that belt. Um, and so
that was that was very exciting. And
then, you know, doing our due diligence,
we saw this Skylake the Skylake asset.
We said, "Wow, this is actually uh this
is also actually an awesome asset." So,
it just got us more excited about this
about this deal.
>> Right. Okay. Let's maybe talk about some
of those specifics as as well and and
the data that you have now. That's also
interesting actually because or maybe
you can actually walk me through what
kind of data you still have from that
from the history and then we can talk
about the specifics on it.
>> Yeah, the data is really uh it's there's
not a whole lot of it. It's dr it's
drill hole data um and it's uh it's
grams per ton over it's just drill hole
data and results. There's no logs,
there's no core. Everything was either
lost or destroyed uh over the years. Um
and so we're just we just Yeah, we just
have this this drill hole database which
has uh XY Z data and assay results that
have been converted from dollars
probably dollars per foot to grams per
ton over meters. Hm.
This when you look at what Tri Origin
wrote in 2017, those reports that that
you inherited as well, they say that the
historic collars have um 2 to 3 meters
uncertainty after grid conversion. They
talk about many uh downhole surveys that
are that are estimates only, geological
logs that are missing for the entire
campaigns and so on and so forth. The
assets cannot be used for a current
resource of course because of how old
they are. What's with what's with all
that? What's wrong with uh what's wrong
with the data?
>> Um
I mean I I think it's just it's it's
just a function of of when and how the
data was collected kind of in the in the
50s and 60s and 70s. Um you know whoever
collected it and the the the uh the
chain of custody and etc etc. know, keep
in mind that was way way way before
43101 and so it was, you know, it was
kind of more the wild west of of of
mining and people were just doing things
however they wanted to do it. um you
know and e even I guess even with all of
this uncertainty um you know even if you
factor in these these uh these uh these
errors um you know the the data still
this the data still got us excited.
>> Okay. Well, it's also well, it's
interesting. I'm wondering really how
reliable that data is because um some
some of the old independent review work
that that previously mapped the Gabro
database and and the intrusions and
invoking the classic units and so on and
so forth. Um those cannot be relocated
in in field work that was done after
that and uh that alteration intensity
could not be traced because of
overburden and whatnot. How are you? I'm
just wondering how how valuable this
data really is is to to you for
follow-up drilling or targeting or
anything like that.
>> Yeah, good question. So, the uh the
drill hole data um that we had uh you
know, we we take it at face value. It is
what it is. Uh we don't I mean we we
don't heavily rely on it. Um that being
said, we did plan our winter 2025 drill
program based on this data. Um and
actually the purpose of that drill
program was twofold. One to see exactly
how much we can rely on this this
historical database going forward. And
two to understand the geology, you know,
because a lot of the data was lost uh
logs, core, etc., etc. Um you know, so
we wanted to get a better idea of the
geology. So we drilled six holes. Uh we
did design the six-hole uh drill program
using the historical data. Um like I
said with the intention of of validating
that that data. Uh what we came up with
was that data is actually it's actually
pretty good. You know we we tested
high-grade zones, we tested medium grade
zones, we tested low grade zones. Um and
you know what we expected is what we
drilled. And so that tells us that this
data is at least half decent.
>> You know, we're not we're not gonna it's
not going to go into a 43101, etc., etc.
Um, but it is data. Uh, it was collected
and, you know, from what we can tell so
far, it's it's it's decent enough to uh
to allow us to use it. Um, to use it,
but not heavily rely on it. Obviously
every every drill hole that we drill uh
you know every modern drill hole is
going to replace any historical data but
you know what we did see with the
historical work is a lot of shallow
high-grade mineralization and you know
so take take that take just that and
that's awesome that's a that's a very
interesting target
>> I actually thought you you didn't drill
what you expected because you drilled it
it was actually better as far as I could
tell because you you say you confirm
continuity over 200 50 m downhole in
that
>> in that one shoot that I talked about at
the beginning as well. But then the
historic models themselves they they
were kind of warning against that that
that the zones could be um less
continuous than than expected or
previously described. So do you think
they were getting something wrong or
like yeah what would happen there?
>> You think they they sorry the question
was are they getting something wrong?
>> Yeah. Were they getting something wrong?
Because they I mean yeah just looking at
how they historically described it was
basically you know watch out this thing
is not going to be continuous. That's
basically what the reports were saying.
>> I mean I think did they get something
wrong? I mean ge geology is there is an
art and a science to geology. Um I I
think uh you know part of part of
geological interpretation is very
um subjective. Uh and you know so
what they knew back then in terms of
geologic models um the research that was
out there the tools that they had uh you
know they may not have had the the
knowledge base to interpret continuity
or maybe the person who who signed off
on it was on the more conservative side.
Um I I don't have a good view into
exactly why they put up the warning
flags. Um you know and that being said
there are a lot of stories where you
know a reinterpretation yields
an incredible deposit. Um you know this
it's it's a classic uh new geology new
new team taking a new look uh not being
influenced by the historical
interpretations. Um, and that yields a
completely different geological model or
a new idea that's to be tested. Uh, you
know, and that's that's part of part of
what we're we're going with at Sky Lake,
>> right? Um, what is the structure
interpretation that that you're running
with right now? I know you're going to
need more data, but yeah, what's the
what's the interpretation?
Uh the interpretation is that there's
these recurring recurring mineralized
shoots along strike. That's
that's the that that's the the very
preliminary
uh interpretation which is something
that's seen in in the Red Lake area. So
it's not it's it's a geological model
that is that has been seen in the area.
Um and like you said, we need we
definitely need more data. Um, but kind
of that's that's the the current very
preliminary operating model,
>> right? Okay. What is the biggest unknown
for you right now? Is it that
>> at Sky Lake? The biggest unknown.
>> Um,
that's a good question. The biggest
unknown, the geologic model. Yeah,
probably the geological model.
Um, you know, if you asked me this 6 to
8 months ago, I might have said the
First Nation situation, but that has
that has nicely come into focus. So,
yeah, I'd say I'd say the geological
model um is is probably the biggest
unknown at this point.
>> What What do you need to answer that
question? Essentially,
>> more drilling.
>> Okay. What is what is the plan for for
the first row campaign here? um after
you solve the First Nations issue like
meterage that that you know drill
spacing, what are you what are you
looking for?
>> Yeah, so we're looking to go back and
drill in winter 2027. So we're looking
at January, February 2027.
Um the First Nations situation feels
like that uh you know we'll will we will
get through that uh that hump which we
can talk about in a bit. Uh in terms of
the program, we're looking at probably
2500 mters, you know, 15-ish holes. Uh
relatively shallow. We're we're the the
plan is to explore a long strike. Uh
yeah, drill shallow holes along strike
and try and get a better idea of of the
uh the geological model.
>> Um any idea of of what the bare minimum
of a program is going to be? And I I do
want to talk about the First Nations for
sure, but just trying to figure out what
the drilling is going to look like and
then and we'll definitely talk about it.
But yeah, how much what's the bare
minimum of drilling it's it's going to
take
>> to pin down the geological model?
>> Yeah. Or just Yeah. your first pass
drill program after you fix the the
First Nation thing.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean, I' I'd like to I'd
like to to drill, you know, I'd like to
drill at least 2,000 meters, ideally
2500.
Uh
yeah.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah, that that that feels like a a
decent amount to uh to get to get a a a
bigger picture view along strike and to
follow up on what we you know the six
holes that we drilled last year
>> and that you would stay focused on that
Kovville patented core then uh or would
you be stepping out along the the
broader anomaly as well?
Uh we pro we it would definitely be
focused on the Koval claim on the Koval
claims. Um I mean currently there's
still a lot of room to explore on the
Koval claims. You know the the the drill
holes that we did last year represented
a very small little postage stamp with
the Koval claims. Um logistically uh
within the Koval claims is definitely
easier. There's a bit of there's there's
a an existing network of trails um
mostly winter trails. So that makes life
a little bit easier for us. Um as well
as it's patented claims. So we don't
necessarily need a drilling permit. We
don't you know the reporting is a lot
easier. Um but we do we would like to
step out of the coal claims whether it's
this drill program or the next drill
program still TBD.
>> How are you going to pick targets beyond
that though? This is and and this ties a
little bit into what you told me
previously when we were talking about
the history here, but there's there's
limited outcrop, right? And then tracing
alteration or or units along strike is
has not historically been super easy
here either. Um overburden there's moss
and whatnot. So yeah, what are what are
your targets for stepping out going to
be based on?
>> Yeah, sorry. I should I should have said
there is soil data going along strike.
There is historical soil soil data that
we have. Yeah, I apologize. I forgot to
mention that.
Yeah,
>> exactly. We'll be using Yeah, the the
the limited drill hole and then the the
soil data that uh that's actually quite
extensive. Um yeah, I haven't I haven't
talked about that yet uh yet today, but
yeah, we do have we do have this data
and it's it's uh you know, as as far as
we can tell, it's it's robust enough for
us to plan a drill hole program.
>> Mhm.
So short-term related the decisions are
are dictated by your relationship with
the First Nations and again we will
touch upon it. I'm I'm building suspense
here if you will, but how does your uh
how does your long-term exploration plan
get influenced by the fact that Beric
can still claw back 51% after a
feasibility study? How does how does
that dictate tempo or or anything else
here really?
>> Yeah, I mean I would I would
I would like to to remove that. Um, you
know, I know that this this structure
was very popular with Bareric
back in the day, uh, where, you know,
prior to the existence of royalties or
the the idea of royalties, that's what
Bareric often did. And I think my sense
is from speaking with other people is
that they do recognize that this is, you
know, this is a barrier to forward
movement or to momentum in the market.
uh and I know that they've converted uh
prior backend rights into royalties and
so that's something that I would I would
be exploring with them at the right
time.
>> But would you have to carry the project
to feasibility yourself or or is there a
strategy where you can kind of force a
decision out of them sooner than that?
>> I don't think we can force a decision
out of them sooner than that. A decision
in terms of converting it to the NSR.
Yes. I think I mean I think that deal
can be done at any time, but in terms of
forcing the decision to back in or or or
wave their right um
I'd have to give that some thought,
>> right? What is the long-term potential
here? Because essentially it is a
capital allocation and a kind of a a
costbenefit analysis if you will. Um
like assuming and yes it's very
assumptions but very forwardlooking but
assuming that the First Nations are okay
with it and the geology works and
financial markets behave as well. How
big could this thing really get
realistically?
>> Um, I mean, I could I think this thing
could get to m multi-million ounces. Um,
you know, depending on the grade uh and
the depth, a multi-million ounce uh
shallow, high-grade deposit, open pit,
that's that's a pretty attractive asset.
um in northwestern Ontario, very well
supported, uh great infrastructure, you
know, it has all the all the ingredients
of of a of a really robust potential
operation.
>> How much drilling do these things
typically get? If you look at is there
maybe a comp of of something that you
could look at and be like, "Yep, we want
to be like them. They drilled that much,
got that kind of a asset."
>> Um I not necessarily. Um there's not a
direct comp part part of it is is we
still don't know exactly what it is yet.
You know, it's still very early stages.
Um but we're trying not to and I think
this this is you know comp a comp for
marketing purposes is one thing.
Internally we prefer not to use comps.
Um you know I find that comps can cloud
judgment. uh you know it can create uh
it can create bias which I you know both
Ludo and myself we are very sensitive to
this to this type of of bias. Um it
exists yeah it exists throughout the
throughout the industry. You know it's
one thing to it's one thing to use other
deposits to try and vector in on your
mineralization um but the it's a fine
line between that and you know
scientific bias. And so we don't we
haven't currently been using a comp at
least internally to to guide us. We're
really using first principles.
>> Well, on those first principles, how
long do you think it could take or how
many how many drill programs would it
take to to get the full potential out of
this thing?
Yeah, I would say
I think we're probably looking at
>> like maybe in meters like if it's is it
is it are we talking 50 or 500,000
meters?
>> Yeah, I was thinking more you know 10 15
to 25,000 meters.
>> Okay,
>> maybe. Okay.
>> I think if we can get a decent idea of
of and I mean you know I I say that
having drilled 1300 meters there. So uh
you know obviously
>> looking absolutely I mean it's it's the
it's a guess to the best of your
abilities. I I I do understand that. Um
>> how let's talk a little bit about timing
as well. also time, money, and risks is
is really what this is spilling over,
but uh into but how how long could it
take for you to get that First Nations
approval? So, this is where you kind of
update me on how are the talks going,
when you think you're going to have it,
and then how long could it take you on
the back of that to actually drill
25,000 mters or 20?
>> Yeah. So, First Nations approval, um
good good time to talk about that. So,
we've been in discussion. I guess uh
maybe I'll get into I'll I'll talk a
little bit about the story kind of what
what happened. Um you know, I think the
viewers may be curious kind of exactly
what happened and and why we haven't
drilled there, which you know
may be slightly off topic, but I think
that has had a a large effect on our
share price. Um and so we drilled our
six holes uh after Pedak in 2025. We put
out some really good results. Seven
grams over 18 meters, four and a half
grams over 16 meters. Um, you know, just
incredible results. We showed
continuity, uh, depth, etc., etc., all
all the good stuff. Very exciting. The
stock almost doubled over the, uh, over
the the the days shortly following the
release. Um,
and then we got into discussions with
the First Nations. Uh that was around
the time that bill C5 came out which uh
you know which put a lot of pressure on
the first nations groups. It removed a
degree of their control and their power
over their land. Um and they were not
happy about it and understandably so.
And so you know the the timing was not
great for us. um you know they they felt
threatened and they not being the
specific First Nations groups that that
we're talking with just they my sense
was that a lot of the First Nations
groups were were getting a little bit
scared and so uh you know we were
approached by or I was approached by the
chief and you know explained the
situation. We had lengthy conversations.
Um,
and uh, at the end of the conversations,
he said, you know, we want you to put
your project on hold until we do what we
need to do on our end to make sure that
our land is protected. Um, and that, you
know, part of that is the uh, the
traditional land use study. Part of that
is negotiating expiration agreement
which had not previously been in place.
Um and I you know I made the decision to
to do that. Um and you know the the the
reason I said I made the decision is
because um as I mentioned earlier we are
operating on patented ground. So legally
we don't actually need to
we don't need to fetch permits. Um and
that really removes the First Nations
consultation from the the whole
expiration process.
uh you know I'm not sure how familiar
the viewers or you are familiar with
that but the uh the first nations
consultation officially is driven by the
government. It's not driven by the the
company. The company is encouraged to
engage with them but officially the
company uh sorry officially the first
nations group sign off to the government
as part of the permitting process. And
so,
um, we did we we did that was we we
don't have to go through that. So, we
don't need this consultation. Um, that
being said, I have a lot of time and
respect for Canadian First Nations
groups and I made the decision to uh to
work with them and put the project on
hold until uh until we got the signoff.
Um, and so, you know, I guess the the
the the biggest challenge uh that we've
had with the First Nations group is
really just time. Um, you know, these
these groups are
uh they are they're they're very small.
Um, you know, and you know, it's it's
really incredible what the chief and
counsel what they deal with. you know,
not only do they deal with, you know,
not only are they the the mayor of the
town, they're also kind of the local
police, they're the uh, you know, they
do they're they're the funeral parlor,
for example. anytime there's a death in
the community, chief and counsel put
together, you know, the ceremony,
whatever it may be in the in their local
group. Um
really everything honestly every single
thing runs through chief and counsel and
so you know they are incredibly
incredibly overworked. uh they have a
lot on their plate always and you know
the reality and as it probably should be
is that deals like ours and mandates
like ours and files like ours get get
put to the bottom uh you know they they
take care of their people first they
take care of their land first um which I
completely understand that being said
it's still you know we're we're we're
just on very different timelines um and
and I'd say that is the biggest
challenge
And so
when when chief asked us to put the
project on hold, uh this was, you know,
about eight months ago, nine months ago,
it was LA Yeah, it was last summer. I
figured I figured a year would would be
good. Um and so far I I I'm happy to say
I think I think I've nailed it. I don't
want to put the cart before the horse,
but uh it feels like it feels like we
should be able to get back in there uh
in the winter and uh and drill.
>> This winter.
>> Yes. Yes. This winter. January, February
2027.
>> Right. Okay.
Yeah. It's going to be interesting to
see how that I mean those are those are
complicated situations most of the time.
So, um yeah, it'd be good to see how
that how that's going to develop. Are
you going to have to raise capital
before that?
>> We will have to raise capital. Yes. This
the Skylake drill program is not is not
fully funded yet.
>> So, you want to raise your own money
essentially. You don't you're not
thinking of um Yeah. You're not thinking
of of JVing it or doing something else
with it?
>> No. No. I I I don't want to JV at this
point at least. I'm I'm not interested
in in JVing Skylink or Blake Log. Those
are the two assets and I guess this goes
back to the the overall company
strategy, but uh Skylake and Blake Block
are my favorite assets and the two
assets that I think will will provide
the the highest probability of the
highest return to our shareholders.
>> So realistically, what does that mean?
So how far away are you from any kind of
meaningful catalysts or or assays here?
Um take all the projects together. I
know we focus on Sky League, but yeah,
what does that realistically mean? How
far are you from again any meaningful
catalysts?
>> Yeah. Uh I mean I think the next I mean
the the you know I think one of the next
meaningful catalysts will be um
hopefully an announcement that the the
the First Nations situation is positive
and we got the green light to move
forward. That will probably come in the
form of you know us receiving permits.
That's kind of the the uh that's kind of
the announcement. Um, which you know I I
can see it's it's a it might be a little
bit confusing because on one hand I just
said we don't need permits to drill Sky
Lake and now I'm saying we we you know
we hope to announce permits. Um let me
explain. We we we will require what's
called a water crossing permit. Um and
that is a permit to access the Skylake
claims. Uh what it is is there's a
couple rivers and uh these rivers are
not within the Cobalt claims. They're
actually not even within they're not
even all within our claims, but um you
know the government still requires us to
get these water crossing permits.
And so receiving that permit will will
uh will will be the announcement. And
then similarly at Blake lock, you know,
we're going to be we're going to be
looking to fetch permits shortly. So
announcing the receipt of permits from
there. I think that'll be a significant
catalyst especially given the story at
Sky Lake where you know it is on pause.
Uh we haven't gone for permits um at the
request of the First Nations. Um and so
that I think will be the next catalyst
and then we're looking at uh you know
winter 2027 uh the loose plan is to
drill three of our assets. Mineric West,
which is our partnership with SOCAM.
That's a fully funded a fully funded uh
drill program. Uh and then we are
looking to drill Sky Lake as well as
Blake Log. And so, you know, we're
lining ourselves up for a fairly busy
winter 2027 with, you know, what we hope
are going to be some uh incredible
discoveries at those three assets going
forward.
Is there no other option to get money in
and and raise capital on the back of a
First Nation announcement though?
Because I suppose that the market might
be waiting for that and and again it's
speculating and forth looking here, but
if you have a First Nation announcement
and then a financing, that sounds like a
better setup than doing a financing
first and and I understand you got to
keep the lights on and and keep your
people happy, but is there nothing you
can do with the other projects or or
create some kind of liquidity from a
from a different spot?
>> Um, no. No, I mean the plan would be to
to raise on the back of a of a of a
positive First Nations announcement.
>> Oh, okay. I was under impression that
Okay, got it. So, you want to raise
before drilling, but you want to raise
after the I got it the other way around.
>> Correct.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Sorry. Yeah. So, I mean,
that was part of the reason for raising
$750,000, you know, a couple weeks ago.
Um, I wanted to get us I wanted that
that was the the minimum amount to kind
of get us through to uh to the next
financing,
>> right? Um, you know, I didn't I didn't
want to raise more at at those levels um
for for obvious reasons,
>> right?
>> Um, so yeah, the plan would be to to to
ride the back of of the cat those
catalysts.
>> Got it. Okay, good. Give me a bit of an
update on the on the other projects as
well. Um Blake, we talked a little bit
about so maybe start with that, but give
me Yeah, give me an update on what else
is going on at the other projects and
what kind of news um might be coming
from there.
Yeah. So, Blake Lock, um Blake Lock, 25
kilometers along the Casabard trend. Uh
a real incredible address. Uh that was
an asset that I consolidated shortly
after I I took over the company
through the New Origin, the New Origin
acquisition.
And really the story there is uh you
know that it it's it's not dissimilar
from Skylake. There's a bunch of
historical work. There's about 200 200
drill holes that we have. Um there's
geoysics, some other stuff. Uh a lot of
historical data that has taken us the
better part of about a year, year and a
half to compile. Um you know, Ludo and I
are uh very technical in nature, very
data driven. Uh and so our priority at
Blake Lock was uh making sure that the
database was was was
sparkly clean. Uh you know and that t
that takes that takes a lot of that that
has proven to take quite a bit of time.
Um and you know following that following
that extent of data compilation you know
then we have to sit around a computer
and figure out what we think is going
on. And so that's kind of what we've
been doing uh you know this winter and
into the summer we were completing some
IP on the eastern part. Uh the western
part of the the asset the IP is
relatively new but the eastern part we
weren't really happy with with what we
acquired and so we redid it. Um
uh and so that has you know that has
helped us out a lot. Um, and the plan
there is, you know, the the current what
what we're doing now and into the uh
into the fall will be drill hole
targeting. Uh, again like I said earlier
with the with the plan of of a uh a
maiden Harfang drill program in winter
of 2027. Similarly, call it 2,2500
meters. Um, in terms of where we're
going to focus there, uh, we're still
actually figuring that out. There's, you
know, there's there's there's really two
parts to this asset. Uh there's the
western part that, you know, what we can
tell is more intrusion related. The
eastern part is uh gold VMS
um more gold VMS type mineralization. Um
you know, they're they're very they're
very different those the eastern and the
western parts. Um and so we're you know,
the the plan is to pick one. Uh the good
news is that it's it's actually it's
actually a tougher decision than uh you
know it's it's quite a tough decision
which I think is a good problem to have
if if both ass if both parts of this
this if both zones are looking so
promising that we're having a hard time
picking which one we want to focus on
first. Um you know that's that's a
problem that I'm I'm I'm happy to have
happy to to discuss adnauseium
internally.
So that's yeah that that's the brief
plan there. Any any questions on that?
>> Uh nope. You can you can you can keep
going. I guess it just kind of makes
sense to list them all and then and and
then maybe if and when you have news we
can do separate conversations on on each
one of those assets because if if I
start going up with follow follow on now
then we'll probably be here for three
hours. So yeah keep keep giving me the
update.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Um so Skylake we already talked
about. Um
>> yeah. Uh moving on to the the rest of
the portfolio. We have Maneric West, we
have Serpent, and we have Egan.
>> So Maneric West, I I briefly touched on
it, so I'll I'll start there. Manic West
is our partnership with SOCM. Uh we're
into our we're getting into the second
year. So far, it's been a great uh a
great partnership. SOCM, I I I don't
have enough good things to say about
SOM. Uh they are Yeah, they're they're
great. They're they're they have
incredible geologists. They're very
sophisticated, very commercial. Uh
yeah, it's they're they're they're great
partners. We're we're we're very very
happy with them. Um the the brief
structure of the deal, it's $3 million
over three years for 50% of the asset.
Um uh and that uh includes or on top of
that is $100,000 uh sorry $200,000 cash
payment to Harfang of which we have
already received half.
Um and so the real the real uh the goal
of this uh of this partnership I guess
the goal of every part of all of our
three partnerships is really to take
this asset to the next level. There's
been a bunch of historical work uh by
Harfang and and you know the previous
owners. Um and you know our plan is to
or I guess what we sold SOM on for this
partnership was uh a bit of a
reinterpretation
um a bit more of an organized
exploration approach. And so far that's
that's turned out to be you know that
that's just it's just going really well.
Um, in the winter we're planning a 2500
meter campaign, like I said earlier,
fully funded by uh as part of the deal.
And uh, you know, just really looking
forward to to to drilling uh to drilling
deeper, no pun intended, into that that
asset and seeing seeing what comes out.
You know, we've done a lot of surface
work over the over the uh over the last
couple seasons.
Um, and we like what we see. We've found
some new zones. Uh we've got a better
idea of of the geology. Uh which is a
little bit more complicated in nature.
Um but yeah, things things are just
going really well. We were there this
summer doing some some uh some kind of
last not last minute but some last uh
last stage follow-up work in terms of uh
pinning down our our our targets. and
you know the the final stage of this
drill hole targeting for the for the
winter program. Uh so that's that's
Mineric West. Moving on to Serpent. Uh
Serpent is the deal. Well, it's the the
we have like you said in your intro, we
have a non-binding LOI with ART. Um you
know, Aramat
is not well known in the Canadian mining
space. Um, you know, I think I mean
they're uh for for anyone who doesn't
isn't familiar with Armet, they're a
French doicile. So they're based I
believe they're headquartered in Paris.
They're traded on the on the Paris
exchange. Uh but they're a they're a
major company uh you know in the
billions uh billions of euro valuation.
They have operations
um they focus on uh they focus on
manganese, lithium, nickel, mineral
sands. You know, I'm just looking at at
my map on this other slide of where they
operate. They operate in on almost every
continent. Um yeah, they have quite
quite a sophisticated group. Um you
know, they one thing I'd like to point
out about that deal is that they do not
currently have anything in Canada. And
so Parfang is their entry into Canada
which um I think makes us special and I
think is is quite significant when a
group like Arame chooses the Harfang and
Serpent asset to as its entry into
Canada. That's you know that's
significant.
>> It it's it's not binding though, right?
So it's non-binding binding. Uh it's
hopefully also not binding but no it's
non-binding and there's no expenditures.
uh expenditure commitments that are
disclosed. There's no, you know, no no
payment amounts, no stop dates, nothing
that I could see. I mean, is there is
there is there something that's
contractually committed already to
Horfang um under this agreement?
>> Yeah, great great point. Let me let me
explain that. I get I actually get quite
a lot of questions about this. Um so
yes, we did we announced a non-binding
LOI. Um and Aramed had asked that we
keep the details confidential until we
sign the definitive and so the current
currently we are working through the
definitive um you know we hope to sign
the definitive in the next I'd say one
to two months um you know that's kind of
been the task of of the summer uh
getting through that uh you know as as a
large corporation um you know I used to
I used to work for larger companies
And so I I understand the you know the
the the due diligence the like mainly
the legal due diligence. We've gone
through all the technical stuff. You
know we've been for what it's worth
we've been we've been in talks with with
uh with ART for the last year and a
half. Um they've come out to the site
they've taken samples back to their lab.
They have a a sophisticated laboratory
that they you know that's that's
internally operated in in France. Um so
the technical due diligence side is is
done. Uh the legal due diligence side
you know with with big organizations can
be quite lengthy and quite indepth and
so uh you know between the legal due
diligence and the documentation you know
these things just take time. Um but the
the hope is or the expectation is that
we will be signing a definitive very
shortly. Uh I see nothing that will get
in the way. Uh it's just you know sim I
guess similar to it to our first nation
situation. It's just it just takes a
little bit of time. Um but yeah so
nothing has been disclosed. Uh you know
what has been disclosed was that is that
they will be taking this or the
agreement will see them taking this
asset through uh through to pea.
>> Um you know so people can infer whatever
numbers they want for that. there will
be a cash payment uh to Harfang over the
the term of the deal. Um it's a it's a
phased approach. I mean it's it's a very
typical option to JV agreement. There's
milestones, there's expectations,
there's cash commitments, expiration
expenditure commitments. Um yeah, it's a
very it's a very plain vanilla option to
JV agreement. Um but yeah, the terms,
you know, the terms just have not have
have not been disclosed yet and we've
agreed to keep that uh keep that to
ourselves until the definitive is. But
rest assured when the definitive is
signed uh everything will get disclosed,
you know, as is typical and required by
the the regulators.
>> You you did initially intend to drill 10
holes there in 1500 meters um in
February, but you only drilled six
holes. Uh it was you call it 1,200
meters. I'm rounding up a little bit. Uh
what happened? Why did you have to stop?
>> Um
that was largely a logistical a
logistical challenge. Um yeah, the
weather uh the weather was challenging.
Uh the drilling was challenging. Yeah,
that was actually that was just, you
know, legitimately a challenging a
challenging program. Um, you know, I
think we always try and
we always try and go out with these
programs uh with expectations that might
be a little bit too high. You know,
maybe 10 holes was a little bit of a
high expectation. Um, but I'd rather
I'd rather Well, I'm biting my tongue
because on on on
one hand, I like to underpromise and
overd deliver. Um, but when it comes to,
you know, when it comes to to to
productivity, uh, you know, to to I I I'
I'd rather prepare for a 10-hole program
so that if it gets to a 10-hole program,
we're not scrambling, you know, if after
five holes,
we still have some more gas in the tank,
uh, you know, then we're we're
scrambling for the next couple of holes.
Whereas, if we plan a 10-hole program,
it's just logistically easier to plan
the tell hole. And if we only get to six
or seven holes, we still have our
program laid out. We still have uh, you
know, we we still have a plan in place.
We don't have to scramble last minute.
Um,
>> so yeah, if that makes sense.
>> What's the realistic time frame on
seeing Serpent Drilled now?
Uh the realistic time frame on seeing
serpent drilled it's going to be
probably I say one to two years. I think
the first step
uh the first step is going to be a a
probably a till program. Um you know
keep in mind this is a lithium deal.
This is not a gold deal. This is a
lithium deal. You know they're they're
not interested in the the gold potential
at Serpent. Um, and so, you know, they
uh, you know, they share our, uh, kind
of I mean, they're probably even more
technically driven than than we are. Um,
to be honest, they they are some of the
most technically driven.
They're they're probably the most
technically driven group that I've I've
come across. Uh, you know, their
technical due diligence throughout the
uh the discussions. Yeah, it's it was it
was incredible. Um very very impressive.
>> Uh so yeah, so they're they're they're
very very technical in nature. Um and
you know, so I think that will, you
know, I think that speaks to the time
it's going to take to actually put a
drill there. You know, there's a lot of
work that can be done and will be done
prior to a drill program. And you know,
as far as I'm concerned, I I agree with
it. You know, I know the I know the
market likes drill programs. Uh you
know, one of the things I I say is, you
know, a lot of the work that we've been
doing has been kind of the the the less
sexy exploration work. You know,
drilling is drilling is what everyone
wants. Um you know, but till sampling,
surface work, it's very important. uh
it's a much better use of capital and
it's very very important in terms of
drilling. You know drilling is drilling
is very expensive. it's very very
expensive and so you know if we have
other tools in our toolbox that are uh
that are a better use of capital um you
know I'm going to use these before I
before I use shareholder money to to
drill the holes even though I know that
that's really that every that's really
what everyone wants and it's you know
it's honestly as the CEO of this company
it's it's a it's a struggle to balance
you know capital allocation versus you
know market market demand or or
shareholder desire.
>> Um, but you know, that's that's that's
just another part of my job.
>> What's a long-term plan for that balance
though, Rick? What do you do you see
yourself as a half prospect generator,
half explorer, or what do you want to do
with that? Because you you do
technically have a prospect generator
portfolio right now? You have those
three assets other than than Skylake.
So, yeah. What are you going what's the
long-term plan for for that side of the
business?
Uh yeah, the long-term plan. I mean,
look, we'll see we'll see how these J
how these option agreements pan out. Um
you know, uh these uh
uh you know, Maneric West,
you know, Maneric West, we're going to
be drilling soon. That'll tell us that
that'll help us talk about the future.
Um
I guess I don't want to put the cart
before the horse. Uh, you know,
the the the short answer is we're going
to have to wait and see. I don't want to
I I I don't think I have enough
information to make those types of
decisions. But I will say that I think
part of part of what we're seeing is
just relative to the stage of the of the
company. you know, soon like once once
we get into drill programs, we'll be
into drill programs and that will be
that will be the company. Um, you know,
my goal is to get a resource on one of
our assets as soon as we can, as soon as
technically possible. I'm not going to
rush these things because I don't think
that resources should be rushed. Um, you
know, and obviously with my background
in resource estimation, I'm I'm very uh
uh I'm very aware of of the mistakes
others have made. Um, and so I don't
want to I don't want to make those
mistakes. Um, but yeah, my goal is to is
to get out of this pre-discovery stage.
Um, you know, and get into a company
that is is drilling assets. um building
resources, you know, and and you know,
or I guess to touch on what I was saying
before, I I'm I'm still not exactly sure
which which which which deposit is going
to be the one that that carries this
company, which deposits, you know, open
brackets, close bracket S, like maybe
maybe it'll be one, maybe it'll be two,
maybe it'll be three. Um, you know, but
part of part of
part of my strategy of of of signing
these option agreements with various
companies is to help us get through this
stage and to take each asset to the next
level.
>> It seems like there's um a couple of
things you're going to have to figure
out first and and you're going to have
to drill a whole lot more before they
can actually become deposits um of
anything that you have here. And that's
basically what we talked about so far.
And it seems like we're going to have,
you know, multiple more conversations in
the future as these things develop and
and we can do deep dives on each one of
them. What keeps you up at night though,
Rick? What is what is the biggest
challenge or the biggest risk for
Harfang right now?
>> Um, the biggest risk
the biggest uh I mean, First Nations is
always is always on my mind. Um, yeah,
it's always on my mind. uh you know just
thinking about
how to manage those relationships. Um
you know you can hire you can hire
consultants that are experts in in
managing these relationships. Uh but at
the end of the day, you know, as as
various chiefs have said, you know, it's
the relationship is is chief to chief.
Um you know, and and me being the chief
of Harfang, it's that relationship that
carries a lot of weight. And so I'm
constantly thinking
um of ways to
of of ways to show up in that
relationship um you know and make sure
that the company is doing the right
thing um you know is is is is
our path forward aligning with uh with
my values the values of the company the
values of the board the values of the
first nation
Um, you know, I'm constantly trying to
understand and educate myself on, you
know, the the history of the First
Nations because I think that's very
important in how they operate, how they
see the world, how they move through
life. Um, you know, it's it's just a
very
it's a very different world. Um, yeah,
it's a very different world, very
different history. And so I I I find
myself constantly just pondering and
philosophizing over over these types of
relationships and and you know the the
history of Canada, you know, I mean I
could I could go on for for a little
bit, but that's definitely something
that that I think about. Um and also
capital. I mean, you know, we we don't
have a lot of money in the bank. Uh I
will be looking to raise money uh for
these jewel programs. I really want
these drill programs to happen and that
is going to require capital and I'm also
constantly thinking about you know who
should I who should I be asking how do I
you know how do I pitch them what's the
story of the company you know because
the the narrative is very important um
and in my previous roles it's not
something that I had to think about um
and so uh I I find myself thinking about
the narrative of Harang and how to
present it and how to position it within
the broader uh junior exploration space
because you know like I said earlier
there's hundreds of thousands of of
companies that have you know
pre-discovery or early stage exploration
assets that are that are competing for
uh for capital. Um, yeah. So, those are
I'd say those are those are the things
that uh that keep me up um at night and
then I just find myself, you know, when
I'm daydreaming, I find myself thinking
about thinking about uh trying to sort
these things out in my head.
>> Yeah, that makes sense. Capital in this
situation is is not easy. So, that's
something that I'll be looking forward
to discussing as well in our in our in
our next interview. I think it's been a
good introduction to the company,
though. Rick, what uh what do you think
I'm forgetting to ask you here? What did
you come here hoping to talk about that
I failed to bring up?
>> Um,
I mean, we covered uh, you know, just
kind of looking through my deck. Um,
I guess one thing we never touched on
was the board. Um, the board and and
management. I would like to just give
give a shout out to the board. Um, and
talk a little bit about them. We have a
great board. uh a lot of a great varied
skill set. We have a couple of
geologists. We have uh you know um Bob
Valiant who who uh who's very
knowledgeable uh in in the uh in his
portfolio and has been a real help uh
guiding us at Sky Lake and and Blake
Lock. um Karen Ree and Sylvie Pudum who
bring a wealth of experience in you know
Sylvie did IR she's incredibly wellconed
and a very good geologist Karen uh Karen
Reese who's the current president of
PDAC uh she's a wonderful resource um
you know helps us a lot on governance um
you know I love talking about press
releases with her and uh that type of
those types of things uh Van Dj
He's the current president of uh of
Earth Labs. Uh he's built a number of
companies and sold or he's you know he
built uh Gold Spot and sold it to uh to
ALS. Um you know, so he's a great he's a
great resource in terms of business
development. Um and JP Jono, he's our
our finance guy. And so we have a lot of
a lot of really good firepower on our
board. uh you know and I and I I rely on
them and and you know and and it's it's
a great they're great resource to have.
Um
>> I'm sure whatever I'm forgetting to ask
you here, people watching and listening
are going to add to that and then
hopefully I get to ask it to you next
time we speak again. This was just an
introduction. So I think it's um yeah, I
think I think it's been good and I
appreciate you covering the board there
at the end as well. Rick, um how much of
the money that you have right now are
you going to spend on marketing? That's
something that we didn't touch upon.
Just looking at my notes. I did want to
ask you about that. Um because I'm just
also wondering like what exactly would
you be marketing right now and uh and
how much money are you going to spend on
that?
>> Yeah, I'm still figuring out exactly how
much I want to spend on marketing. Um
you know, I mean, I'm sure a lot of
other CEOs in in similar roles can can
attest that, you know, we get five
marketing emails a day. uh you know
trying to sell us on everything. Um and
so it's it it is quite overwhelming uh
the marketing world out there trying to
figure out which conferences are good
you know which conferences are good
specifically for for this type of
company. Um
and so I'm still I'm still working
through that. Uh that's that's a task
that uh
uh that I'm working through. But
marketing is something that I've learned
is very important. Um, you know, and
again what I was saying earlier to your
previous question of what keeps you up
at night, you know, it's part of it is
is the marketing, the the narrative. Uh,
so I don't I don't have a a number, but
we will be marketing um, you know, I
will be marketing the deal uh, sorry,
the deal. I will be marketing the drill
programs.
Um, you know, we we will be raising
money. So, uh, I will be looking looking
to the market for for some capital to
drill and that'll probably be the focus
of my of my marketing over the next, you
know, in at least couple months.
And then following that, I hope to have
a steady stream of results. You know,
we'll be drilling three projects that
comes with a yeah, hopefully a steady
stream of positive results. And that's
uh, you know, positive results are
probably the easiest thing to market.
What about when you talk to those
people? What's the biggest criticism you
typically get when you go out there and
try to market the company in person?
>> Yeah, the biggest criticism is the
identity of the company. Um, what are
you trying to do? You know, where's the
focus? What's the focus? Give me an idea
of your business, of your of your
strategy. Are you a project generator?
Are you an exploration company? And so,
you know, it's taken a little bit of
time to to to kind of put everything
together. Uh, you know, but I think over
the last two years between the deals
that we've signed, um, and the assets
that we've been working, um, I I feel
good about, you know, bringing focus to
the company and saying, "All right, you
know, Skylake and Blake lock, we're
focusing on these. we have these option
these option agreements that are going
to uh you know move this bucket of
assets to the next level. Um but the
real focus of the company and what's
going to bring the most value to
shareholders are going to be Blake Lock
and Skylake and they're both you know
they're both very early stage
prediscovery and uh you know that's
that's the goal to to make a discovery.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Fair enough. And and I mean
these are early stage stuff so there's
always a lot of push back to give you
on. Um I think we talked through
>> Yeah. Go ahead. Oh, I was going to say
also the the size, you know, like this
the size the size of the company is it's
not uh you know, you have to have you
have to have the right appetite for uh
investing in a $5 million pre-discovery,
you know, junior exploration company.
And you know, for definitely for some of
the funds, uh you know, a lot of the
push back I get is, you know, I I like
the story. I I I get the vision, um but
you're a little bit too small. you know,
we we don't like to write we're not in
the business of writing such small
checks. Come back when you're a little
bit bigger.
>> Yeah, fair enough. Um well, that that
was exactly why I was so surprised that
there's so many Quebec institutions in
it, but now that you've given me the
history of the of the company, that does
make sense. Um yeah, I think I've been
through most of it. Um I guess I'll I'll
get out of your face now and then
hopefully you and I can uh sit down for
uh for a conversation once you have some
more data and and some more clarity on
on timing and whatnot. it'd be good to
um to do another deep dive, but for now,
really appreciate your time. Thank you
so much for sitting down with me today.
>> Yeah, thank you. It's been uh it's been
it's been great to tell you more about
about Octan.
>> Before everyone leaves though, I still
have a couple of more things to say. The
fact that this company was interviewed
here today doesn't mean they're
necessarily a good nor a bad company.
We're not here to endorse or attack
anyone. We're simply here to ask a few
questions. If you find that we have
failed in asking a question that you
would have liked to hear an answer to,
please let us know by emailing
Antonioresource.com
and we will try to correct that mistake
in a future conversation. If you made it
that far, you probably know this, but I
will remind you nonetheless. Mining is a
risky business. Losing money is the norm
and should be the expectation as mineral
exploration, development and extraction
is an extremely risky industry where the
performance of individual companies
typically depends on many different
moving parts including company specific
factors like geology, financing ability,
hiring methods and many others as well
as other things that are outside of the
company's control like geopolitics,
macroeconomics, commodity prices and
many more. Too many to list here really.
Moreover, these companies are typically
in the pre-revenue stage, which means
they rely on the public markets for the
financing of their operations, which
often results in shareholder dilution.
They raise money by issuing new shares.
Even if the CEO promised they won't have
to raise capital anymore, I've seen it
over and over again. It still can and it
does happen. Which is why you need to
stop and think. You need to do more
research and not rely solely on what the
company tells you. Furthermore, as a
general rule of thumb, you'd be better
off understanding that all company
communications, albeit this interview or
their website, their presentation, their
news releases even, and of course their
social media and everything else, all of
that is intended as marketing. And
although we at Resource Talks do not
make buy or sell recommendations, even
if you ask us, we just don't do that
because there is a clear conflict of
interest given the nature of our
business which sells content producing
services to these companies. Even though
we don't do that, many accounts and
channels out there do do that. Exactly.
They do give out direct recommendations
even though they are often paid for
opinions and they're worth just as much
as you paid for them, which is to say
nothing. And you should be aware of that
in bias. You should not blindly trust
people on the internet. That bias is not
always going to be clearly disclosed
with everyone out there. So it's just
safer for you anytime you're watching
any type of company specific content to
approach it with a dose of skept a big
dose of skepticism and just assume that
the party telling you about it is biased
oftentimes in multiple ways. They might
own shares, they might be paid by the
companies or I should say they often are
and that bias is not always going to be
clearly disclosed with everyone. So,
always ask yourself what the incentive
of your counterparty is and never rely
on them regardless of their incentive,
but instead double check if what they're
saying is true by using setter plus.ca.
Unfortunately, at least in my
understanding, nobody out there has any
special predicting abilities. The CEOs
don't possess any superior knowledge and
they cannot know about what's going to
go up, what's going to go down, or
what's going to go in circles. And none
of us know whether any of the company's
activities that we discussed today will
result in a success. Again, given that
we're talking about very high-risisk
activities where most of the times it
ends in failure. The vast majority of
the times it ends in failure. Also,
unfortunately, try we won't always catch
all red flags or all challenges with the
company. So, even if we did ask a few
tough questions in in this conversation,
don't rely on this being all of the
important and tough questions. Again,
these are complicated startups with many
moving parts. They require rigorous
rigorous I'll try that again. But they
require rigorous due diligence.
Resource talks and its hosts cannot
guarantee the quality of anything
presented in this video. And you cannot
hold the company, the channel, or its
host responsible for any losses or
damages stemming from the way you decide
to use the information you're just
presented with. Viewers, listeners, and
readers acknowledge and agree that the
information presented herein does not
constitute a solicitation or an offer to
buy or sell any security or instrument
or to participate in any trading
strategy. Resource talks and all parties
involved in the management of this
business strictly disclaim any and all
liability for losses and or damages
whether direct, indirect, special or
consequential or other consequences
howsoever caused arising out of any use
or reproduction of the content published
and distributed by resource tax or any
decision made or action taken in
reliance upon it. By consuming this
content, all viewers vowed to release
resource talks and all parties involved
in the management of the business from
all claims, proceedings or consequences.
You know, this is all to say it's a lot
of lawyer talk just saying you should
not blindly trust us or anybody else on
the internet and you should always do
your own research as cliche as that may
sound. Once again, social media is meant
for entertainment. Setterplus.ca
is where you do your research. That's an
official government website. That's
where you find the company's official
filings. And I encourage you to read and
analyze the management information
circular, the financial statements, the
management discussion and analysis, and
whenever available, the NI43101
technical documents at the very least.
If you don't understand everything in
those documents, the chances of you
losing money are even higher than they
normally are in this space. As mentioned
earlier, the chances of even the best
analysts in this sector losing money are
very high since this is venture capital
and it is not for everybody. I'll leave
you with one of Charlie Munger's quotes
which I wish I'd listened to more often
earlier on in my career which says,
quote, "If you don't understand it,
don't do it." Unquote. Thank you all for
listening and I wish you a great day
ahead.